These are essential skills for us, our families, our communities.
They're also critical to the workplace.
In my research, when I looked at what helps people to bring the best of themselves to work,
I found a powerful key contributor, individualized consideration.
When people are allowed to feel their emotional truth,
engagement, creativity, and innovation flourish in the organization.
Diversity isn't just people, it's also what's inside people.
Including diversity of emotion.
The most agile, resilient, individuals, teams, organizations, families, communities
are built on an openness to the normal human emotions.
It's this that allows us to say, what is my emotion telling me?
Which action will bring me towards my values?
Which will take me away from my values?
Emotional agility is the ability to be with your emotions, with curiosity, compassion,
and especially the courage to take values connected steps.